Some families have all the fun.
Addams Family Reunion is a comedy, horror, fantasy film directed by Dave Payne.
The Addams Family goes on a search for their relatives.
Gomez and Morticia are horrified to discover that Grandpa and Grandma
Addams have a disease that is slowly turning them "normal".
The only chance they have of a cure is to find a family
member hoping that they know a home remedy.
Gomez Addams, played by Tim Curry.
Morticia Addams, played by Daryl Hannah.
Phillip Adams, played by Ed Begley Jr..
Lurch, played by Carel Struycken.
Walter Adams, played by Ray Walston.
Grandpa Addams, played by Kevin McCarthy.
Addams Family Reunion is a 1998 American comedy film based on the
characters from the cartoon created by cartoonist Charles Addams.
Directed by Dave Payne, the film was intended to serve as a pilot for
a new proposed television series produced by Saban.
The film stars Daryl Hannah and Tim Curry as Morticia and Gomez Addams respectively, while Carel Struycken
and Christopher Hart's hand are the only ones to reprise their roles from the last two films.
The film's plot focuses on the eccentric, macabre aristocratic Addams family mistakenly arriving at the wrong family
reunion and encountering a man (Ed Begley Jr.) who seeks to commit murder in order to inherit a fortune.
Payne had intended to give the film a dark, edgy tone.
However, Saban had interfered with the development, insisting that the story be aimed solely at
entertaining children, and lack much of the black comedy and satire of the previous films.
Saban also wanted Payne to imitate aspects of Paramount Pictures' popular 1991–1993 duo of films, and the
1964 TV series, and rejected any original idea developed by Payne and the film's screenwriters.
As a result, the film was poorly received by critics, who criticized the film's screenplay, special effects, production design, and
much of its acting, while singling out Tim Curry's performance for praise, calling Curry the best part of the film.
The film explores themes of hotel, butler, family relationships, campy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.